demandstudiossucks.com 2012-05-25

# Privacy Policy « Demand Studios Sucks

#### Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to Demand Studios Sucks (DSS). To better protect your privacy we are posting this notice to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To ensure this notice is easy to find, it will be available on our homepage and on every other page within the site where personally identifiable information may be requested.

#### Google Adsense and Other Advertising Providers

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, DSS has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

#### Collection of Personal Information

When visiting DSS, the IP address you use to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. Comments posted to our blog entries will require a valid email address, in addition to the preceding information. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### DSS Forums

Additional privacy policies for the DSS forums may be accessed at:  
<http://www.demandstudiossucks.com/forum/ucp.php?mode=privacy>

#### Links to third party Websites

We include links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these third party websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

#### Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Demand Studios Sucks then you may contact us via [our contact page](http://www.demandstudiossucks.com/contact).

Last updated Sun, 14 Aug 2011 19:36
